f-prot.com 2017-11-30

# FRISK Software International's Privacy policy - F-PROT Antivirus

### CYREN�s Privacy Policy

Effective date:  July 7, 2014

This Privacy Policy covers and describes how CYREN Ltd. (�CYREN�) collects, uses and disclosure of information we collect through our FRISK software and our website

[www.f-prot.com](file://pfsvaus1/jlawson$/Program%20Management/3-Projects/Privacy/www.f-prot.com).  The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged CYREN.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy or practices or have an unresolved privacy or data use concern, please contact us at [legal@cyren.com](mailto:info@cyren.com).   ** **

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Cookies**

 �Cookies� are small data files that are written to and stored on your hard drive when you visit a Web site; they do not read files on your hard drive. Like most Web sites, we use cookies to personalize a user�s experience of our Web site and to make it easier for users to complete forms. Our cookies do not track user movement once you leave our Web site.

Most Web browsers allow the user to be notified upon the proposed installation of a cookie and the user can then decline the cookie. Even if you decline the cookie, you may continue to use our entire Web site.

We use data and information received from our cookies for marketing research purposes, to improve the site�s content and structure, for example, to potentially revise or restructure our Web site for easier and more intuitive movement throughout. We may also use the information to evaluate our site�s technical capacity in order to improve it. 

Currently, the data and information we collect with cookies is reviewed in an aggregated form, which is not personally identifiable. We also correlate the data and information received from cookies with personally identifiable information, to identify specific users and track their Web site usage.  Whether or not the data and information received from cookies is correlated to any specific user, we do not and will not disclose, sell, rent or share any data or information derived from cookies with any third parties.

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user�s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers� personally identifiable information.  

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see �Choice and Opt-out.

We use cookies to personalize a user�s experience of our Web site and to make it easier for users to complete forms.  The use of cookies is covered by our privacy policy.  We do have access or control over these cookies.

Our service provider use cookies to make it easier for you to complete order forms for our F-Prot Antivirus software. The use of cookies by our service provider is covered by our privacy policy.  We do have access to these cookies.

**Aggregate Information**

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and analyze user trends. This includes reviewing data and information contained in log files located on our Web server, which record the date and time of each visit to the site, the user�s IP (internet protocol) address, the referring URL (the prior Web site visited) and the files viewed on our Web site (including HTML pages, documents downloaded etc.).  Our FRISK software also logs download traffic information generated by the F-Prot Antivirus updater component.

We do not disclose, sell, rent or share any information derived from log files with any third parties.

Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Registration to the Site**

Although you may generally use our site without providing us with any personally identifiable information, for some services � such as downloading trial or free versions of F-Prot Antivirus software, submitting support requests and signing up for F-Prot Antivirus alerts services - you may be asked to voluntarily provide certain types of personally identifiable information. The types of personal information collected on these pages include:

  * Name
  * Company (for business customers)
  * Department (for business customers)
  * Customer number
  * Email address
  * Country / Territory

When purchasing F-Prot Antivirus software, the following personal information may be collected:

  * Payment information (i.e., Credit card, PayPal, Bank Transfer or Check)
  * Credit card�s expiration date
  * Credit card�s owner name
  * Credit card�s security code
  * Mailing address

We use this information to conduct market research and analysis; Improve our web site and marketing efforts; Process orders for F-Prot Antivirus software; and to, Send you marketing communications.  

We may supply general, region-specific customer information to our trusted resellers and/or distributors to assist them in providing high quality local services to our customers.

The information you submit to [www.f-prot.com](http://www.f-prot.com/)  is stored in a database to enable you to return without re-registering as well as sales and marketing purposes. Your �logged-in� status may be saved in your browser via a cookie. Either way, the personal information that you submit will be saved by CYREN; we do not share this information with any third parties for any reason, unless agreed by you explicitly on the registration form you completed or unless disclosure of such information is necessary to fulfill certain legal and regulatory requirements such as to comply with a subpoena or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others� rights or to prevent harm.  If CYREN is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Choice and Opt-Out**

The only users that will receive ongoing correspondence from CYREN are those that specifically request a subscription to the F-Prot Antivirus Alert service.  We do, however, reserve the right to contact registered users from time to time, and within reason, for example, to offer our services to relevant potential customers or partners or relevant marketing material to our users.  We will not, however, send unsolicited messages to users of our site who indicate that they do not wish to receive such messages. If you do not wish to receive unsolicited email messages from us, please contact us at unsubscribe@cyren.com.   Every marketing-related email sent by CYREN includes the option to unsubscribe.

**Links to Third-Party Web Sites**

Through our Web pages, you may connect to third party Web sites via hyperlinks, and the connections may or may not be obvious. We are not responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing or disclosure of data and information by such third parties. We encourage our users to be aware of the varied privacy policies of Web sites that they visit.

**Your Right to Review & Modify Data & Information**

You have the right, at any time, to review, delete and/or modify any of your personally identifiable information that you provide during registration, or any other voluntarily provided information. To do this, edit your profile on the site or by emailing our Customer Support at [info@cyren.com](mailto:info@cyren.com).   To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have applied reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, due to technological limitations and the risk of unlawful interceptions and accessing of transmissions and/or data, we cannot completely assure you, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable data and information, and any other electronically communicated information, will be absolutely confidential. 

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information on our site, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Please remember that you play a valuable part in security as well. Your password to access our site, which you select at registration, should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. And, after you have finished using our site, you should log off and exit your browser so no unauthorized persons can use our site with your name and account information.

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please call us at +972-9-863-6888 or email us at [legal@cyren.com](mailto:info@cyren.com).  You may also contact us at:

7925 Jones Branch Drive  
Suite 5200  
McLean, VA  22102

Attn:  Chief Privacy Officer
